Alastair Low



Online Portfolio: http://alastairlow.co.uk
Personal Games: http://lowtek.games

12 Cleghorn Street flat 3R, Dundee DD2 2NR

DOB: 20/04/1991 Mob: 0790 606 96 20 email: lowtek@hotmail.co.uk

About Me:

I am a games Artist/Designer. I specialise in non-photorealistic styles. I have been making games since I was in primary school and continue to work on hobby games whenever I'm not playing games. I am on the board of the SGDA. I'm also into making, moding and 3d printing.

Skills:

I am a good problem solver who is punctual and motivated. I like to learn and am good at working in groups, working to deadlines and working on my own.

Intermediate	Competent	Experienced (10 years +)
zbrush	Maya	Blender 3D (15 years+)
Graphics Gale	3dsMax	Photoshop (13 years+)
Dreamweaver	Illustrator	Unity 3D (8 years+)
Gimp	Adobe Flash	
Krita	Adobe Premier Pro	
Sign Lab	Adobe After effects	

Shipped Games:

SAS 4 Zombie Assault (Ninja Kiwi)

Bloons Super Monkey 2 (Ninja Kiwi)

Bloons Monkey City (Ninja Kiwi)

Bloons Adventure Time TD (Ninja Kiwi)

Counter Snipe (Ninja Kiwi)

Red Reign (Ninja Kiwi, apple arcade)

A Familiar Fairy Tale: Dyslexic text Based Adventure Game. (Lowtek Games)

Upcoming Games

Flea! A nes game for the original NES, funded on Kickstarter. (Lowtek Games)

Relevant Experience:

Ninja Kiwi: July 2013 – Present

Artist - Work in small teams to make 2d and 3d artwork for mobile games. Helping create pipelines.

Alastair Low CV 2020 Mobile: 790 606 96 20 email: lowtek@hotmail.co.uk

SGDA (Scottish Game Developers Assosiation): July 2019 - Present

Board Member – Provide networking and community events and information for developers ion Scotland. I help organise events such as play parties, game jams, presentations and panels.

Dundee MakerSpace: 2017 – 2019

Director – Helped organise our local community non-profit makerspace. Performing inductions on 3d printers, laser cutter and other tools. Making marketing materials and logos and recruitment.

Dsigns: May 2008 – 2013 (Contract Work)

Worked in a small sign making workshop where I designed and manufactured several types of signs for shops business. Worked in illustrator and Sian Lab and learned how to work to client briefs.

Education:

BA (Hons) Computer Arts (First) University of Abertay Dundee Honours project the aim was to emulate traditional 2D styles in a real-time 3DGame engine.

HND Computer Art (A) Central College Glasgow

Awards and exhibits:

Worked on Bafta nominated game Bloons Adventure Time TD

Oor Wullie's big bucket trail, Painted the Game art Wullie.

EGX Rezzed 2020 leftfield collection with A Familiar Fairy Tale.

College 2010: Best student of the year award.

Ludum Dare 25: 2nd place for the Graphics category. (Game: You are the Dragon)

Creative Loop Award 2013: Best interactive media Artefact.

Interests:

I like Playing and Creating Video Games. I enter game jams as much as I can either in teams or on my own. I like to collect things such as old consoles, games, 3d printers, toys, Pop-Up books and various weird musical instruments. I like watching movies and making movies, vlogs and tutorials.

References:

Dsigns:

Elsi Duncan D Signs Limited 41 John Player Building Kerse road, Stirling

FK7 7RP

Tel: 01786 470305

Kenneth Fee:

Kenneth Fee Mprof Program Tutor University of Abertay Dundee **Kydd Building** Bell Street, Dundee

DD1 1HG

Tel: 01382 308000

e-mail: K.Fee@live.abertay.ac.uk email: signs@dsigns.co.uk

Alastair Low CV 2020 Mobile: 790 606 96 20 email: lowtek@hotmail.co.uk